<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>rajaSahil</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on rajaSahil</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 23:15:00 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//localhost:1313/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 23:15:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/about/about/</guid>
      <description>Meet Sahil (rajaSahil), an experienced backend developer passionate about building scalable solutions and contributing to open source projects.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 id="about-me">About Me</h2>
<p>Hey there! I’m Sahil, also known as rajaSahil in the online world. I’m a backend developer with over 4 years of hands-on experience, specializing in Golang, Rust, Kubernetes, microservices architecture, and distributed systems.</p>
<h3 id="expertise">Expertise</h3>
<p>I excel in crafting scalable solutions to optimize performance and reliability in backend applications. My technical skills include:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Programming Languages:</strong> Golang, Rust</li>
<li><strong>Technologies:</strong> Kubernetes (k8s), Docker, microservices architecture, SQL, NoSQL, gRPC</li>
<li><strong>Systems Design:</strong> Building resilient and scalable distributed systems</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="open-source-contributions">Open Source Contributions</h3>
<p>I am passionate about open source and actively contribute to projects that enhance features and improve performance. Some of the projects I&rsquo;ve contributed to include openEBS and KubeArmor.</p>
<h3 id="get-in-touch">Get in Touch</h3>
<p>I’m always open to new opportunities and collaborations. Feel free to reach out if you&rsquo;re interested in discussing backend development, open source projects, or product innovation.</p>
<p>Let’s connect and innovate together!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
